Deck.create(id: 10, name: "Just Jedi Things")
Card.create(question: "In the Jedi code, what follows from the line 'There is no passion, there is ________'", answer: "serenity", deck_id: 10)
Card.create(question: "In the Jedi code, what follows from the line 'There is no chaos, there is ________'", answer: "harmony", deck_id: 10)
Card.create(question: "What is the name of the power that the Jedi use", answer: "the force", deck_id: 10)
Card.create(question: "What is the name of the faction that reprsents the evil equivalent of the Jedi", answer: "the sith", deck_id: 10)
Card.create(question: "On what planet is the Jedi temple located", answer: "coruscant", deck_id: 10)
Card.create(question: "What is the name of the planet that the Jedi order was founded upon", answer: "tython", deck_id: 10)
Card.create(question: "What is the physical weapon of Jedi", answer: "lightsaber", deck_id: 10)
Card.create(question: "After being granted the title of Jedi Knight, a Jedi may choose to study further into one of three branches, what are those branches. Which of the three branches focuses upon physical attributes and protection?", answer: "Jedi Guardian", deck_id: 10)
Card.create(question: "After being granted the title of Jedi Knight, a Jedi may choose to study further into one of three branches, what are those branches. Which of the three branches focuses upon their cerebral force skills?", answer: "Jedi Consular", deck_id: 10)
Card.create(question: "After being granted the title of Jedi Knight, a Jedi may choose to study further into one of three branches, what are those branches. Which of the three branches focuses upon a mix of physical and force skills, while adding pragmatic abilities such as mechanics and computer skills?", answer: "Jedi Sentinel", deck_id: 10)
Card.create(question: "What is the title a teacher bestowes upon their apprentice within the jedi order", answer: "Jedi Padawan", deck_id: 10)
Card.create(question: "After the fall of Emperor Palpatine, what is the name of the last remaining Jedi Knight", answer: "Luke Skywalker", deck_id: 10)

